So, for example, if this is the case, then we should do this, right?
Yes, yes, yes. And then, what should we do there? Up to down, right?
Meaning, what is most important? How much money will we get?
How much interest rate will we get? How much tenure will we get?
And what is left to right? The importance of the column.
So, what does it mean?
While filling this form, I become intelligent.
You are thinking that you are going to hit me.
Yes, yes. I don't have to explain anything to you.
I directly understand that this happens due to property value.
And this is the most important property, the tenure.
And you can use just colors and sequencing and order, right?
Yes, yes.
Okay, if you apply it, then it will change.
Maybe not most important at this moment.
But it should be done.
Okay.
Let's talk about adjustability.
That it should not disappear like this.
And there is no problem if it is pre-filled.
Let's arrange all these tooltips.
Let's not read all the tooltips.
I haven't read it myself.
No, read it.
Yes, read it.
Let's imagine that
The majority of the public is stupid.
Like...
The public doesn't believe in science.
There is a shortage of people who don't believe in science.
There is a shortage of people who take realistic decisions.
There is a shortage of people who take non realistic decisions.
Who take the decisions of politicians, who make the decisions of politicians.
Basically, the maximum number of people who come to us,
the maximum number of people who come to us,
but those who come non realistic,
we have to impress them.
And we have given attention to such detailings.
And even if they have such detailings,
they are not impressed.
And we just have to climb their ladder.
We start with most non-stupid.
We gradually come to stupid.
We make our solution foolproof.
Foolproof is not F-U-L-L.
F-U-L-L is foolproof.
What is waterproof?
What is airproof?
F-U-L-L is foolproof.
What is fool?
Fool is fool.
Foolproof is not F-U-L-L.
Foolproof is foolproof.
I have never heard of F-U-L-L.
Foolproof is not foolproof.
Foolproof is foolproof.
And then we slowly become foolproof.
So now you don't have to do full appreciation.
But you have to appreciate it.
How did Tesla go to mass market?
So don't worry.
As long as we can get some traffic.
And some smart people have come to us.
Who really need it.
There is a cognitive load.
I don't know if you know.
The way you showed me.
I don't know.
The sentences I tell you.
The cognitive load increases.
The first sentences we had.
Structure.
No commission.
No bias.
This cognitive load increases.
Because it has to load a lot of context.
But you said this.
No bias.
Priority treatment.
Sponsorship.
I mean...
Suppose you can't imagine this.
No x, y, z.
Versus you said.
No x, no y, no z.
This cognitive load has increased.
Because in 9.
x, y, z.
But these two 9 extra.
What did they do?
Increase the cognitive load.
We don't know anything.
People have a normal thinking process.
Or there is a way to understand the language.
There is a way to think.
We have to make words that fit that.
That means we don't have to increase the load.
So we have to give the information that fits that.
So what is the problem?
I mean...
Compare all and apply in one shot.
And banks will compete for you.
The load has increased.
Compare and apply. Let banks compete.
The load has decreased.
That means banks will compete.
Once you compare and apply.
The load has increased.
Banks will compete.
I have to put a lot of effort into it.
Does it mean anything to you?
It is like...
The trend of modern training data.
If you use
the same practices.
The training of the model needs to be less.
Versus you have to customize it.
Then you have to train it.
This is it.
I mean...
Model is more likely to follow
what kind of instructions.
And I use the same instructions.
Instead of customizing it.
I mean...
The trend of the model is to open the PR first.
Then write the code.
Then open the PR.
I mean...
The load of the model is reduced.
This is what I mean.
We see how people are trained.
People usually train left to right.
Up to down.
We do the same.